Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education In Asia Records, Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum A
1904-1983
RG 11A
Yale University Divinity School Library
115
(285 boxes)
Record Group No. 11A represents a continuation of the official archives of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, supplementing and overlapping with the papers in Record Group No. 11. These archives document the work of the United Board as it sought to redefine its policies and goals following the closing of mainland China in 1951. It provides extensive information about the institutions and projects to which the United Board lent its support. Following the Communist takeover in China, the United Board extended its educational work to other Asian nations, establishing the support of Christian institutions in Hong Kong, India, Indonesia, Japan, Korea, Pakistan, the Philippines, and the Republic of China (Taiwan).
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Biographical / Historical
1951 Following the severing of contacts with the China colleges, goals of the United Board for Christian Colleges in China were redefined. The new "Program for Advance" included the following elements: 1. Fellowships for graduate study in North America and in East Asia for potential Christian Chinese leaders; 2. Visiting professorships and Chairs in Asian universities for Christian Chinese scholars; 3. Research and publication related to Christian higher education; 4. Assistance to agricultural education in the Philippines. The Board's program was divided into three sections: Services in North America, Research and Publication, and Services in Asia.
1951 Sep Chung Chi College opened in Hong Kong, supported financially by the United Board.
1951-1955 Plans made for the creation of a new Christian college in Taiwan, Tunghai University, which opened in September, 1955.
1954 Council on Christian Higher Education in Asia (COCHEA) established in cooperation with the Asia Committee of the National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A. COCHEA was terminated in 1958.
1955 May United Board for Christian Colleges in China corporate name changed to United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia.
1956 May New committee structure implemented: four Standing Committees - Policy, Nominations and Administration, Investment and Banking, and Promotion; three Area Committees - Taiwan/Hong Kong, Southeast Asia, Mainland; five Functional Committees - Agricultural Education, Medical Education, Research and Publication,
Literature Program, Fellowships. 1957-1960 The United Board experienced financial difficulties due to exhausted reserves and hesitant support.
1962 Policy approved for wider geographical outreach with increased emphasis on activities serving more than one institution and on those of a short-term nature.
1966 The United Board had established continuing relationships with the following institutions: Chung Chi College in Hong Kong, Philippine Christian College in the Philippines, Satya Watjana Christian University in Indonesia, Silliman University in the Philippines, Soochow University in Taiwan, Tunghai University in Taiwan, Yonsei University in Korea.
1966-1969 Appraisal of Christian Higher Education in Asia conducted with funding in part from the Harvard-Yenching Institute and the Luce Foundation.
1967 The U.S. Foreign Area Claims Settlement Commission awarded the United Board $3,464,379 in response to claims filed for damages at seven colleges in China during the Second World War.
1968 China College funds held by the Court for eighteen years were released for use "Cy Pres", meaning "as nearly as possible" in conformity to the original intent of the donors. These funds amounted to three and a half million dollars.
1970 Commission for the Advancement of Christian Higher Education in Asia (CACHEA) established with support of newly released funds. This commission was Board-financed, but autonomous.
1970-1973 Thirty-five Christian colleges and universities and fifteen other organizations in the field of higher education in thirteen Asian countries benefitted from 112 projects sponsored by CACHEA.
1974 UBCHEA restructured. New committee structure included: an Executive Committee, four Administrative Committees (Finance and Administration, Investment and Banking, Development, Nominations), Program committees as required.
Scope and Contents
II United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia,Consolidated General File
III New File
IV College Files
V Audio-Visual Materials
VI Related Organizations and Publications
These records are a continuation of the official archives of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia. Transferred to the Yale Divinity Library in 1984, they supplement and overlap with the records of the United Board found in Record Group Number 11. Group 11A documents the work of the United Board as it sought to redefine its policies and goals following the closing of mainland China in 1951. It provides extensive information about the institutions and projects to which the United Board lent its support. The records comprise 115 linear feet of material dating from 1904 to 1981, with a concentration on the period 1958 to 1971.
Portions of Record Group Number 11A could have been directly integrated into files found in Record Group Number 11, but because of the bulk and complexity of the two groups, it was decided to treat them as separate entities. The registers for Groups 11 and 11A should be used in conjunction with each other. There is documentation in Record Group 11A that relates directly to the China colleges and universities that were the focus of the United Board's work prior to 1951. Of particular interest in Series III are the articles and papers gathered by the United Board in connection with a proposed book on the China colleges. These papers touch on subjects such as women's education in China and science instruction at the China colleges and universities. Series III of Group 11A also includes records related to the Japanese War Claims made for each of the Board-supported China colleges and universities. Also of note are the Princeton-in-Asia files found in Series VI, which document the longstanding Princeton connection with Yenching University; some files previously in Group 11A have now been transferred to the Princeton-in-Asia office in Princeton.
The researcher should be aware not only of the interrelatedness between Groups 11 and 11A, but also of the interrelatedness between the series within Group 11A. A researcher interested in Yonsei University, for example, would need to consult not only the Yonsei University files in Series IV, but also Series II for correspondence of individuals involved with Yonsei, Series III for United Board committee records and for information collected in connection with the Appraisal of Christian Higher Education in Asia, Series V for photographs, and Series VI for documentation of Yonsei found in the files of the Council on Christian Higher Education in Asia. Some cross referencing has been used to point out cases of diffused documentation, but a general awareness of its prevalence in this collection is also advised.
There is no Series I in Record Group No. 11A. Series II has been established as a continuation of the Consolidated General File found in both Series I and II of Group 11. These files represent the office files of the New York headquarters of the United Board. The materials remain in their original arrangement, filed alphabetically by the names of individuals, organizations, or subject headings. Notable correspondents in Series II include: Rowland Cross, William P. Fenn, Lyman Hoover, Paul T. Lauby, Elisabeth Luce Moore, George L. Paik, Elsie Priest, Henry Knox Sherrill, Hollington Wong and Henry P. Van Dusen. Also of interest are the files organized under the heading "Mission Boards", which document the problems faced by the various boards during this time period and their evolving relationships with the United Board. Though it is primarily correspondence, the Series also includes working papers, miscellaneous typescripts, legal documents, and some publications collected on specific topics or by individuals. The Series includes documentation of organizations related to the United Board, some of which are also documented in Series VI.
While the Consolidated General File of Series II is predominantly correspondence, Series III consists primarily of official papers, minutes, and reports. The compilation of materials in this "New File" provides a succinct overview of the development, operations, and internal structure of the United Board during a turbulent period of its history. Much energy was spent on redefining the Board's purposes and in promoting the new goals and programs among potential donors. Approximately 1H linear feet of material in this Series relates to the United Board for Christian Colleges in China; this material largely overlaps with material found in Series III of Record Group No. 11. The remainder of the Series relates to the numerous committees of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, to program efforts such as the Appraisal of Christian Higher Education in Asia (conducted 1966-1969) and the Commission for the Advancement of Christian Higher Education in Asia (1970-1973), and to financial matters, particularly the Japanese War Claims funds and the so-called "Cy Pres" funds, monies designated for use in China Colleges, which were frozen by the Court following the closing of China and finally released in 1968 for use in other United Board programs.
Correspondence, minutes, reports and publications in Series IV document the formation, policy, and programs of colleges and universities in Asia that were associated with the United Board. Material from eighteen institutions is included, but the files are most extensive for the following schools:
Chung Chi College, Hong Kong (9 linear ft.)
Yonsei University, Korea (16 linear ft.)
Silliman University, The Philippines (18 linear ft.)
Tunghai University, Taiwan (13 linear ft.)
Yonsei University was formed by the merger of Chosen Christian College and Severance Union Medical College; these predecessor institutions are also documented. The audio-visual materials of Series V are largely related to the four institutions best documented in Series IV. Also of interest is a photograph album documenting the early work of Princeton-in-Asia.
The related organizations documented in Series VI include:
India Association for Christian Higher Education
Christian Colleges Association
Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia
Council on Christian Higher Education in Asia (COCHEA)
Princeton-in-Asia (Princeton-in-Peking, Princeton-Yenching Foundation)
Smith-Ginling
Wellesley-Yenching
The records are most extensive for COCHEA. Seven linear feet of materials related to the Princeton-in-Asia program once included in this Series have now been transferred to the Princeton-in-Asia office in Princeton. These files are still described in this finding aid, to provide information; they date primarily from 1923 to 1949 and include committee records, correspondence, promotional material, and publications. In conjunction with the Princeton-in-Peking records found in Record Group No. 11 and the personal papers of Dwight Edwards (YDSL Record Group No. 12), Sidney Gamble, and Lennig Sweet (YDSL Record Group No. 8), these records provide very complete and valuable documentation of the Princeton-Yenching connection.
The Related Publications found in Series VI are divided into two categories: Concerning Education and Conference Publications. These publications represent material collected by the United Board as background material or as documentation of conferences that the Board sponsored.
Arrangement
II. United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia,Consolidated General File
III. New File
IV. College Files
V. Audio-Visual Materials
VI. Related Organizations and Publications
Religious education -- Asia; Universities and colleges -- Asia; Educators; Chong Ji shu yuan (Hong Kong, China); Council on Christian Higher Education in Asia (U.S.); Dong hai da xue; Princeton-Yenching Foundation; Silliman University; United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia; Yŏnse Taehakkyo
- United Board Consolidated General File -- Addendum, 1959-69; Series II
  - Adams, Louise B. (Mrs. John E.), Bequest, 1959-69 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adamson - Afong, 1962-65 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Education, 1950-57 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Development Council - Agricultural Missions, Inc., 1953-70 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ai - Allen, May Alice, Estate of, 1958-71 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alli - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China (see also: United Service to China (through '66) ABMAD - USC merger (1966)), 1960-70 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American-Korean Foundation, Inc. - Amherst, 1958-69 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amsterdam Avenue (731) Property, 1962-63 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, C. - Anderson, W., 1960-70 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ang - Anglican Church, 1958-70 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Appleton, F. G., Jr. Sr., 1961-71 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Appraisal of Christian Higher Education in Asia (see: New File Addendum - Series III)
  - Arc - Asia Foundation 1, 1958-71 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Asia Christian Colleges Association (see also: Series VI), 1956-70 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Asia Christian Colleges Association, minutes, Conference of Missionary Societies in Great Britain and Ireland, 1958-61 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Asia Foundation, 1958-71 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Ateheo - Atherton, F. C. Trust, 1946-71 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Atherton, Juliette M., Trust, 1959-71 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Atkinson Foundations - Atwood, 1958-71 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Audit (see: Price Waterhouse Co.)
  - Austin College - Bab, 1958-68 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bai - Bal, 1959-71 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bam - Banister (Jessie C.), Shantung Trust, 1958-71 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bank of America - Bankers Life Co., 1959-71 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bao - Barnett, Eugene E., 1959-71 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Barr - Batchelor, Charles and Rosanna, Memorial, Inc., 1965-71 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bates - Bea, 1959-71 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bec - Becker, Stewart, 1964-71 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bee - Beech, Miriam D. (Mrs. Joseph) and daughter Katharine, 1959-70 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Beem - Berea, 1958-70 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Berger, Marie Cole, 1967-71 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bertholf - Bersama, 1962-71 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Billingsley - Bingham, 1960-69 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bishop, Donald G.- Bishop, Irl, 1965-71, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bittinger - Black, Donald, 1959-71 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Black, Mrs. Kenneth - Blackney, 1959-71 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Blankenhorn - Blatchford, 1962-71 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bloomfield - Borton, 1959-71 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Bosch, Arthur - Bouck, 1962-71 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bovenkerk- Boynton, J., 1959-71 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Bragg - Brlggs, 1958-70 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Bristol - Bromund, Werner, 1958-70 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Brooks - Brown, Mrs. Van Sant J.; Brownell, 1958-71 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Brumbaugh, Rev. Dr. Thoburn T., 1959-75 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Brush - Buck, J, 1962-71 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Buell, Rev. Mrs. William - Bunker Sydney K., 1960-68 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Burgess - Burke, 1959-70 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Burr - Byler, 1958-71 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Cady, Dr. Lyman V. and Irene - Calderon, Cicero, 1963-71 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Caldwell, Oliver J. - Calhoun, Wanda, 1958-70 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - California Academy of Sciences, 1957-71 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Calk - Cameron, J. A, 1958-71 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Canadian Dept. of Revenue - Carr, Alden J., 1958-70 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Carson, Dr. Arthur L. Edith, 1956-72 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Carter, Wenda - Cartwright, Dr. Frank T., 1956-65 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Cas - Central College, Pella, Iowa, 1959-71 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Central Philippines University, 1963-71 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Chai - Chalmers, 1958-71 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Chambellan, Berger Welti (Audit), 1958-59 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Chamberlain, M. - Chan, K. S., 1954-67 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Chan, Man-wai (Maynard), 1957-65 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Chan, P. - Chang, Chi Wen, 1959-70 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Chang, D. - Chang, Mrs. Suen-i Wu, 1957-68 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Chang, T. - Chang, Wei-Ming, 1956-70 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Chao, Kang, 1957-62 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Chao - Chen, Caroline, 1958-70 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Chen, Cheng En-Tsi - Chen, Hugh En, 1957-67 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Chen, Pai-fun (James), 1955-70 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Chen, K. P. (80th Birthday Scholarship, Willow Chen Memorial Endowment Scholarship), 1961-71 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Chen, M. - Chen, Chin-Shan (Stephen), 1961-66 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Chen, S. C. - Chen, Theodore Hsi-en, 1955-71 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Chen, W. - Cheng, H., 1956-69 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Cheng, Paul - Cheng, T. Y., 1957-69 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Chester, R. - Child, Louise Avery, 1959-71 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - China Colleges - China Institute, 1965-70 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - China International Foundation (see: International Foundation)
  - China Medical Board of New York, 1955-71 (Box 6, Folder 71-72)
  - Ching, H. H. - Chitambar, J. B., 1958-68 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Cho, Won-Kyung, 1963-69 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Choate, Helen A., Estate - Choi, B. H., 1956-63 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Chou, Leland and Lily, 1960-70 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Chou, S. - Christian Character of Christian Colleges, 1957-70 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Christian Faith and Higher Education Institute; Christian Study Centre on Chinese Religion, 1961-67 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Christian Higher Educatlon ln Asia Fund (see: New File - Addendum - Appraisal of the Protestant Christian Effort in Higher Education in Asia)
  - Chu, Chee Kong - Chu, Richard; Chu, Robin, 1957-67 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Chu, Yu-Kuang (see also: Ind. file for Chu's proposal - Student Exchange), 1955-71 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Chung-ang University, Seoul, Korea - Chung-Yuan Christian College, Taiwan, 1960-68 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Churchill, Irvlng L. and Kathryn, 1957-70 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Churchman, Charles J. and Pat, 1958-61 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Clapp, Margaret - Claremont Colleges, Clark, Russell I., 1961-66 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Clements, Robert M. - Cochran, Nancy Ann, 1959-68 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Coe - The College of Physicians and Surgeons of Ontario, 1960-67 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Coles, J. Ackerman, Estate, 1955-64 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Coles, J. Ackerman, Last Will and Testament, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Colley, Mary - Colllngs, Vlncent, 1959-67 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Collins - Comfort, 1960-68 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Commission for the Advancement of Christian Higher Education in Asia (see: New File Addendum)
  - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Committee on New Patterns see: New File Addendum - Appraisal of the Protestant Christian Effort in Higher Education in Asia, 1958-60
  - Conference of British Missionary Societies, 1958-61 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Conference on Christian Higher Education in Asia (see: New File Addendum - Appraisal of the Protestant Christian Effort in Higher Education in Asia)
  - Congdon, Elizabeth, 1958-61 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Connelly - Consulate General of the Republic of China, 1958-67 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Cook - Coolidge, E., 1957-66 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Coolidge, H. - Council of Protestant Colleges and Universities, 1958-67 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Council on Christian Higher Education in Asia (see: Series VI Addendum)
  - Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs - Cronin, A. E., 1958-64 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Crose, Kenneth L., 1959-60 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Cross, Laura B. Memorial Fund, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Cross, Rowland M. ( see also: Chinese Student and Alumni Services and Fellowship Program), 1954-60 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Crummley - Curran, Jean A., 1959-64 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Cushman Estate - Cuyler, 1952-64 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Daniels - Dalton, Jack, 1959-64 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Danton - Darby, 1958-64 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Dartmouth Project Asia (see: Brumbaugh, T. T. (1965 Feb 24))
  - Dauderman - Davis (Arthur Vining) Foundation, 1956-67 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Day - Decker, John W., 1958-63 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Dei - Denlinger, Rev. Mrs. Paul B., 1958-63 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - De Saint, Phalle Memorial Rosamond Fund - De Young, Christ, l958-64 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Dickison - Down, 1958-66 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Dunlap - Dy, Juanita, 1957-66 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Dyde - Ensign, David, 1955-65 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Estoreo - Evans, Mr. Mrs. A. Murray, 1958-64 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Eversole - Faucett, Lawrence, 1958-67 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Fehl - Fenn, R., 1958-65 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Fenn, William P., 1955-63 (Box 9, Folder 112-116)
  - Fenn, William P. (see also: New File Addendum - Appraisal of Christian Higher Education in Asia), 1964-70, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 117-120)
  - Fenske - Ferguson, Mary, 1958-65 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Fiduciary Counsel, inc. - Fitzgerald, 1946-68 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Flaherty, Donald W., 1966-71 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Fleming, John R. - Fok, John S. K., 1957-64 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Fong - Ford Foundation, 1959-61 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Forkner - Fredrickson, 1956-67 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Freedom House Bookshelf Committee, Freeman, Mansfield, 1958-64 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Frei - Friends, 1958-60 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Frick, Bertha, 1962-64 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Frick, Bertha--Report of Libraries in East Asia, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 129A)
  - Fromm - Fugh, Philip, 1958-66 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Funston - Gayo, 1958-66 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Gefeno - Geng, Y. H. (George), 1958-64 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Gibbs - Ginling Alumnae Welfare Fund, 1958-64 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Ginling Association in America, Newsletter, 1955-61 (Box 11, Folder 134-135)
  - Ginllng College Direcrory - Ginling Girls Middle School, 1951-60 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Gleason - Goodrich, L. Carrington, 1959-64 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Gordon, Ernest, 1959-64 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Goucher, John F. - Gowing, P. G., 1960-63 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Graduation Certificates, 1959-64 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Graham - Gregory, 1958-68 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Griesy, Grinnell College, 1957-61 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Gropius, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Grose, Robert F. ( see also: Silliman University), 1962-1965 Jan (Box 12, Folder 143-144)
  - Gulliksen - Gupta, Brijen, 1958-62 (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - Hackett - Hall Estate, 1928, 1952-67 (Box 12, Folder 146)
  - Hall, V. - Hamilton College, 1958-67 (Box 12, Folder 147)
  - Hamlin, John - Hao, W. H., 1961-65 (Box 12, Folder 148)
  - Harbison, E. H. - Harrison Township Property, 1957-64 (Box 12, Folder 149)
  - Harshbarger - Harvard, 1958-67 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Harvard Yenching Institute (see also: Yonsei, Chung Chi,Tunghai-Series IV), 1959-64 Jun (Box 12, Folder 151-152)
  - Harvard Yenching Institute, 1964 Jul- 1972 (Box 13, Folder 153-156)
  - Harvard Yenching Research Project, 1961 Jul- 1964 Jun (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Haskin - Hazen Foundation, 1958-66 (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - Hazlett - Heimburger, Leroy F. Fund, 1957-61 (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - Helfferich, Reginald H. (see also: Evangelical Reformed Board of International Missions), 1959-64 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Hellberg - Hess, 1958-62 (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - Hibbard, D. - Hibbard, Hall L., 1958-63 (Box 13, Folder 161)